

CATALIN BABALAU Web developer

O Chisinau, Moldova

☑ catalin.babalau@yahoo.com

% 0786 00 299

SOCIAL

in @catalin-babalau

f @catalin-babalau

@ @catalin-babalau

@onitel

<> CodeWars

EDUCATION

Web Development

Zero to Mastery Academy on Udemy

Feb 2021 - Present

Erasmus Mobility

SMK University of Applied Social Sciences, Vilnius Lithuania

Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

General Management

State University of Pitesti, Pitesti Romania

2015 - 2018

Math and Sciences track

"Moldovan-Finnish" High School, Chisinau Moldova

2013 - 2015

SKILLS

• Html

JavaScript

• CSS

Git

• React •

C#/.NET

React Hooks

0 // / .. 12 !

Bootstrap

PostgreSQL

Mailchimp

PROFILE

I am a young IT specialist passionate about Programming, History and Economy. I consider myself as an adaptable open minded person with a critical thinking.

I like solving problems and I always say that for every problem there is at least one solution.

EXPERIENCE

Lifeguard

From Jun 2016 - Oct 2016 | High Sierra Pools Inc.

Washington DC, USA

oGCDP crew member (Volunteering)

From Nov 2015 - May 2016 | AIESEC

Pitesti, Romania

Customer support - Client service (Volunteering)

From Dec 2013 - Jan 2014 | Anrome SRL

Chisinau, Moldova

PROJECTS

Calculator CSS background generator

CSS HTML JavaScript

Source code

Source code

See Live See Live

To do list Timer

CSS HTML JavaScript

Source code

See Live

CSS HTML JavaScript

Source code

See Live

Free Souls Custom

CSS HTML Bootstrap MailChimp

Source code See Live

Robo Corporation

CSS HTML REACT
Source code
See Live

LANGUAGES

• Romanian (native)

English (B2 - C1)

Russian (B2 - C1)

• Spanish (A2)

INTERESTS